<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Oruggt</string>
    <string name="flood">If you are caught in a flood, follow these safety measures:\n
    • Do not walk through moving water. As little as 6 inches (15 centimeters) of moving water can make you fall.\n
    • If you have to walk in water, wherever possible, walk where the water is not moving. Use a stick to check the firmness of the ground in front of you.\n
    • Do not drive into flooded areas. If floodwaters rise around your car, abandon the car and move to higher ground if you can do so safely.\n
    • Do not touch electrical equipment if you are wet or standing in water.\n
    • Avoid floodwaters; water may be contaminated by oil, gasoline, or raw sewage. Water may also be electrically charged from underground or downed power lines.</string>
    <string name="earthquake"> If you are caught in an earthquake, follow these safety measures:\n
    •	Stay calm! If you\'re indoors, stay inside. If you\'re outside, stay outside.\n
    •	If you\'re indoors, stand against a wall near the center of the building, stand in a doorway, or crawl under heavy furniture (a desk or table). Stay away from windows and outside doors.\n
    •	If you\'re outdoors, stay in the open away from power lines or anything that might fall. Stay away from buildings (stuff might fall off the building or the building could fall on you).\n
    •	Don</string>
    <string name="earthquakee">\'t use matches, candles, or any flame. Broken gas lines and fire don\'t mix.\n
    •	If you\'re in a car, stop the car and stay inside the car until the earthquake stops.\n
    •	Don't use elevators (they'll probably get stuck anyway).</string>

    <string name="tsunami">If you are caught in a tsunami, follow these safety measures:\n
    • When in coastal areas, stay alert for tsunami warnings.\n
    • Learn details of the local warning systems.\n
    • Plan an evacuation route that leads to higher ground.\n
    • Know the warning signs of a tsunami: rapidly rising or falling coastal waters and rumblings of an offshore earthquake\n
    • Never stay near shore to watch a tsunami come in.</string>
    <string name="cyclone">If you are caught in a cyclone, follow these safety measures:\n
    •	Disconnect all electrical appliances. Listen to your battery radio for updates.\n
    •	Stay inside and shelter {well clear of windows) in the strongest part of the building,
    i.e. cellar, internal hallway or bathroom. Keep evacuation and emergency kits with you.\n
    •	If the building starts to break up, protect yourself with mattresses, rugs or blankets under a
    strong table or bench or hold onto a solid fixture, e.g. a water pipe.\n
    •	Beware the calm</string>
    <string name="cyclonee">\'eye\'. If the wind drops, don\'t assume the cyclone is over; violent winds
    will soon resume from another direction. Wait for the official \'all clear\'.\n
    •	If driving, stop (handbrake on and in gear) - but well away from the sea and clear of trees,
    power lines and streams. Stay in the vehicle.</string>

    <string name="draught">If you are affected by draught , follow these safety measures:\n

    1.	Save water. Repair all the faucets that drip, and fix any leaks in the pipes in the household.\n
    2.	Try to collect as much rainwater as you.\n
    3.	Take shorter baths and showers.\n
    4.	Use dishwashers and washing machines for fully loads only.\n
    5.	Do not flush tissues. Instead, throw them in the trash.\n
    6.	Do not waste water while waiting for hot water. Instead, collect and save it.\n
    7.	To prepare your lawn for a drought, plant flowers and shrubs with similar watering needs together.</string>

    <string name="landslide">If you are caught in a landslide, follow these safety measures:\n
    •	Stay alert and awake. Be aware that intense, short bursts of rain may be particularly dangerous, especially after longer periods of heavy rainfall and damp weather.\n
    •	Remember that driving during an intense storm can be hazardous. If you remain at home, move to a second story if possible.\n
    •	Listen for any unusual sounds that might indicate moving debris, such as trees cracking or boulders knocking together. A trickle of flowing or falling mud or debris may precede larger landslides. Moving debris can flow quickly and sometimes without warning.\n
    •	If you are near a stream or channel, be alert for any sudden increase or decrease in water flow and for a change from clear to muddy water.\n
    •	Be especially alert when driving. Bridges may be washed out, and culverts overtopped. Do not cross flooding streams!! Turn Around, Don</string>
    <string name="landslidee">\'t Drown!.\n
    •	 Embankments along roadsides are particularly susceptible to landslides.\n
    •	 Watch the road for collapsed pavement, mud, fallen rocks, and other indications of possible debris flows.\n
    •	Be aware that strong shaking from earthquakes can induce or intensify the effects of landslides.</string>
    <string name="logpg">Welcome to Oruggt\nIndia\'s 1st all-in-one safety app\nPlease Sign Up to continue</string>
    <string name="cred">1037930970544-dbp4q234cailuai5mbc7risqidncqgug.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string-array name="blgp">
        <item>SELECT BLOOD GROUP</item>
        <item>A+</item>
        <item>A-</item>
        <item>B+</item>
        <item>B-</item>
        <item>O+</item>
        <item>O-</item>
        <item>AB+</item>
        <item>AB-</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="filtyp">
        <item>Image</item>
        <item>Video</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
